A Guide to the Kathleen Kirk Collection, ca. 1722-2013
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Kathleen Kirk Collection, ca. 1722-2013
The Library of Virginia
50542, 50929, 51190
21 reels of microfilm
Kirk, Kathleen
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Loaned for duplication by Kathleen Kirk, 8 August 2012 and 8 November 2012 (50542); 5 June 2013 (50929); and 6 February 2014 (51190).
Scope and Content
TO BE ADDED.
Contents List
- Accession 50542 - Kathleen Kirk Collection, 1751-2008., Extent: 9 reels of microfilm. (Reel 6129-6131, 6201-6206)
  - Vol. 1, David Robertson (1785-1856) and Elizabeth Steele Thompson (1799-1888), 1751-2008. (Reel 6129)
  - Vol. 2, John Todd Anderson Martin (1812-1859) and Elizabeth Bruce Robertson (1836-1915), 1785-1974. (Reel 6130)
  - Vol. 3, Jesse Thornhill Davidson and Elizabeth Bruce Robertson Martin, 1780-1990. (Reel 6131)
  - Chassie Belle Martin Abbitt Thomas papers, Vol. 1, Book 1: Charles Arthur Plunkett Abbitt and Chassie Belle Martin, 1881-1955. (Reel 6201)
  - Chassie Belle Martin Abbitt Thomas papers, Vol. 2, Book 2: Chassie Belle Martin Abbitt and Cornelius Thomas, 1881-1955. (Reel 6202)
  - Chassie Belle Martin Abbitt Thomas papers, Vol. 3, Book 3: Chassie B. Martin letters, 1881-1955. (Reel 6203)
  - Chassie Belle Martin Abbitt Thomas letters, news clippings, and photos, Vol. 1, Book 1, 1873-1888. (Reel 6204)
  - Chassie Belle Martin Abbitt Thomas letters, news clippings, and photos, Vol. 2, Book 2, 1889-1990. (Reel 6205)
  - Thomas Shipyard (Portsmouth, Va.) time book, 1889-1890. (Reel 6205)
  - Kirk family papers, 1859-1925. (Reel 6206)
  - Robertson, Staples, Thompson, Barnett papers, 1768-1890. (Reel 6206)
  - Robert Lawrence papers, 1839-1866, undated. (Reel 6206)
- Accession 50929 - Kathleen Kirk Collection, 1722-2013., Extent: 6 reels of microfilm. (Reel 6207-6212)
  - J.J. Kirk family volumes, Book 1: Elias Kirk and Rachel Paul, 1722-2013. (Reel 6207)
  - J.J. Kirk family volumes, Book 2: John Jacob Kirk and Margaretta S. Godwin 1722-2013. (Reel 6207)
  - J.J. Kirk family volumes, Book 3: Children of J.J. Kirk and Margaretta S. Godwin, 1722-2013. (Reel 6208)
  - Gill family papers, Book 1: William Gill and Frances Rowlett Eanes, 1796-2013. (Reel 6209)
  - Gill family papers, Book 2: Robert Sidney Gill and Aphia Jane Clements, and children, 1796-2013. (Reel 6210)
  - Gill family papers, Book 3: Robert Henry Gill and Margrette Adams Goodson [Madge], 1796-2013. (Reel 6211)
  - Gill family papers, Book 5: Robert Henry Gill and Margrette Adams Goodson [Madge], 1796-2013. (Reel 6211)
  - Gill family papers, Book 6: Thomas Goodson and Martha Persons, 1796-2013. (Reel 6212)
  - Gill family papers, Book 7: James Wheadon and Sarah Cocke Graves, 1796-2013. (Reel 6212)
- Accession 51190 - Kathleen Kirk Collection, 1885-2011., Extent: 6 reels of microfilm. (Reel 6230-6235)
  - John Russell Kirk and Arthur "Merle" Abbitt, Book 1, 1904-1906. (Reel 6230)
  - John Russell Kirk and Arthur "Merle" Abbitt, Book 2, 1885-2001. (Reel 6230)
  - John Russell Kirk and Arthur "Merle" Abbitt, Book 4, 1895-1931. (Reel 6231)
  - John Russell Kirk and Arthur "Merle" Abbitt, Book 5, 1931-1970. (Reel 6232)
  - J. Stokes Kirk and Margaret Gill Kirk, Book 1, 1912-1937. (Reel 6233)
  - J. Stokes Kirk and Margaret Gill Kirk, Book 4, 1926-1942. (Reel 6234)
  - J. Stokes Kirk and Margaret Gill Kirk, Book 5, 1943-1990. (Reel 6235)